

Mohammad Imam Rifai

+62 85 624 355 323 Imamrifaibisnis@gmail.com Patrol, Indramayu

Social Media

Maspalul









Summary

I am a creative, artistic and ambitious Graphics Designer with a talent for thinking outside the box and coming up with innovative ideas and designs. I graduated with a 1st Class honours degree in Graphic Design from Kingston University and subsequently have worked in the design industry for the past 2 years. I pride myself in providing excellent service to all stakeholders and seeing the positive impact I make in people's lives and businesses.

Working Skills

Javascript





Tailwind

Project Experience

JUNE 2014 - aUGUST 2016 / aRT DIRECTOR AT VENGAT STUTIO

- · Developing marketing strategy for studio clients
- Cooperation with all level digital agency
- Creating brand identity

JUNE 2014 - aUGUST 2016 / aRT DIRECTOR AT VENGAT STUTIO

- · Developing marketing strategy for studio clients
- · Cooperation with all level digital agency
- · Creating brand identity

JUNE 2014 - aUGUST 2016 / aRT DIRECTOR AT VENGAT STUTIO

- · Developing marketing strategy for studio clients
- Cooperation with all level digital agency
- · Creating brand identity

Hobby

% Football



Education

JUNE 2014 - aUGUST 2016 / aRT DIRECTOR AT VENGAT STUTIO

- · Developing marketing strategy for studio clients
- Cooperation with all level digital agency

JUNE 2014 - aUGUST 2016 / aRT DIRECTOR AT VENGAT STUTIO

· Developing marketing strategy for studio clients